[{"answer": "I wouldn't have a chance.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Just don't play with her with tennis, right?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Have you seen the president, by the way?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "You'd (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "This one is always boy crazy.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "Who was more boy crazy?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "That's what I'm saying, Piers.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "What more can a man give you?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "You're on a CNN show, right?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I fancy myself a news guy.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "What is the serious side of Mario like?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I think it was just a strong work ethic.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "What were the values?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "It's still the land of opportunity.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "What do you think attracted them to America?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "You know, it's funny.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "What do they make of what happened to America?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Brush them.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Can she not even say, Mario, what have you done to your teeth?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "You know, I think we have no one to blame, really, but ourselves.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "OPEZ: I am because I got to spend time with him.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Are you a fan of the president?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "He was on my show, believe it or not.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "He was on your show?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "I think you still have the same issues, to tell you the truth.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Is America more or less racist for having had its first African-American, nonwhite president?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "The same friends I got right now.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "What are your old friends maybe from the old neighborhood when you get back there?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "The reality right now, the barber shop talk, if you will, everyone is concerned about jobs -- jobs, jobs, jobs, jobs.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What are their biggest concerns in reality, do you think?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "And your show sort of fits, you take celebrities to meet their haters, right?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I've been bothered by the way it affects my family.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Have you been particularly hurt by the stuff you read about yourself?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Oh, nothing too terrible.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "What's the worst stuff for you to deal with?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "As a guilt ridden Catholic boy, you've been this lady, the mother of your child for three years now?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "It's coming.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Are you going to get married?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "It is?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I was not mature enough and I didn't have the guts really, probably, to do the right thing.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "How did you get married for two weeks?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Those sort of things become redundant and yes, I have.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Do you think you've met the one now?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Yes, Mario Lopez.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "Do I have it in me?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "That's pretty good.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Mario, do you think you have it in you?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Oh, God!", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Mario the lothario, do you think you have it in you?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "That's about 4,000 women.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Ten percent?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I'm honored by those rumors.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Is that the kind of job you would love to have?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, you know -- I've, like in, I filled in before.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Are you in discussions for the job?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Yes, of course I did.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Did you see me?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Out of the 27 reasons I want to hate you, is because you're a great dancer.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "I, too, had the opportunity to interview him and talk to him and found him to be a really nice guy and very down to earth.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "What do you think as a former contestant and someone in the world of entertainment?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Well, just in general, again, that hate is not good and you should sort of take the time to sort of get educated on the topic, the person, what he's been through, and you took a giant leap forward to commit to doing something like \"Dancing with the Stars\" -- knowing that he is a smart guy, knowing all that would come with it.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What would your message be to those people?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Good, thank you.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "Hopefully, life will make sense one day.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What will make sense?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "I do believe that some things will happen.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Do you have any confidence of that?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Originally I laughed at it.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What was your take looking back on it?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Did they not really understand the culture that you were talking about?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I mean, he just thanked me for attending and I thanked him for inviting me.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What did he say about it all?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I definitely knew that he would definitely then do -- they didn't do the research on Common.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "But anyway, what did you make of it?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "I tend to differed with believing that he didn't fulfill the hope.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What's your view on how he's performing?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I believe that if we can instill in them self-love -- because obviously if we give a child some hope through education and through fulfilling their dreams, then they will like keep their eyes on the prize.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "What is the one thing you think that really needs to be fixed that hasn't been fixed?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "I definitely believe that builds a great foundation.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "But is it as simple as that?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Well, yeah, I would say to anyone who feels that through a gang is where they can find love -- you have to look at the results of people who join gangs.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "What do you say to those people who just see a gang as the only place to find anyone that cares about them?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Making films.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "If I told you could only do one thing the rest of your life, you could write poetry, you could write make or you could make films, which one would you take?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I try to put things in perspective.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "But how do you deal with all that, all the attention you get?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "I mean, without wishing to intrude at all, Common, you weren't responsible for Serena Williams' temper tantrum the other day on the court, right?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I wouldn't have a chance.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Just don't play her at tennis, right?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I'm well.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Christina, how are you?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "No, sir.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Do you wake up every day looking in the mirror thinking, you're the sexiest woman alive?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "ORGAN: I loved that \"Esquire\" interview, because it had so many lovely nuggets in it.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "I think ugh, what do I have to do today?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "He is.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Is he as ridiculously romantic as he seems?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "That's very sweet of you to say.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "How does he deal with the fact that there are million and millions, if not billions of men around the world now who are coveting his wife?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "People have been very positive and complimentary, which is really nice.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Does it annoy you?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "There's a kind of slight dilemma there, isn't it?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Do you think we are in a much better place now?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "I think that we are in a much better place now.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Or do you think that kind of overt, male dominated regime still exists?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Jack.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Thinking of you?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "This movie is based on Allison Pearson's (ph) book \"I Don't Know How She Does It.\"", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "What is this all about?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Um, I -- my conclusion after talking to so many women who have seen the film is that everyone's take is different.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "What's your conclusion?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "Not right now I'm not.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "You must be tempted to see a little patter of mini- Hendricks' feet, aren't you?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "I really look at working mothers, all mothers, to be honest, in awe.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Does that concern you?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "If he saw you take the money, and he saw you get in the car, then why didn't he say anything?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "How are you feeling about that, lucky?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "I love your optimism right now.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "And thank Donald Draper for all his terrible behavior?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "110916pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "It has to be just straight, right?", "qSentId": 789}]